Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Natalie Rogers, events planning.
Yes, Mrs. Miller.
I confirmed the
venue this morning.
You're all set for
your Christmas party.
Natalie Rogers,
travel consultant.
Hey, Mr. Walker,
how were your flights?
I'm so glad.
Yeah, you know,
you can always string some
lights
around a palm tree and
call it Christmas.
Natalie Rogers,
custom gift-wrapping.
Yes, I will be dropping those
off in about
15 minutes.
Mr. Ortiz!
I finished the wreath
for your food truck.
Even if the weather is
frightful,
the chilies will keep you warm.
Look.
Muchas gracias.
Wendy!
Oh!
Christmas cards, addressed
and stamped.
Oh, I...
Pop them in the mail and the let
the mailman do the rest.
Thank you so much,
they're beautiful.
Oh, I love hand-addressed cards,
but with my penmanship
no one would get them until
July.
Well, I threw
in a couple of extra
for Joshy and Becca
direct from the North Pole.
They'll be thrilled.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
- Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas, Wendy.
Yeah, took a little
creativity but you know
I love a challenge.
Merry Christmas.
Natalie, Sparky would be so glad
to see you.
Come here.
Sparky, your favorite
sitter is here.
Hello, handsome.
And these clothes.
Who doesn't love to get all
dressed up for the holidays?
We want to take him on a
Christmas cruise,
but he gets terrible
sea-sickness.
Well, I am happy to.
We are gonna have a great time!
We're gonna watch
It's a Wonderful Woof,
and lap up eggnog, and sing
Christmas carols.
See, he already knows
the opening to Jingle Bells.
You're the best pet-sitter
anywhere we've ever had.
Thank you.
Natalie, thank you so much
for doing this.
Of course.
Are you sure I can't convince
you to come work for me?
Thank you, but
I already have a job.
You have eight jobs.
That was just the
last time I counted.
May have added
one or two since then.
But why can't I since
I'm the Jacklyn of all trades.
When are you gonna settle down
on one career?
I don't know, but I figure
when I find the perfect thing,
I'll know it.
And until then
I'm happy as I am.
Well, I hope
you're not still waiting
on the perfect thing
to do for Christmas.
Thank you, but
I'm gonna spend Christmas
with my cousin Olivia.
I should probably get going.
Miles to go before I sleep
or at least a few more blocks.
Be a good doggie, okay.
Merry Christmas.
Let's go, Sparky.
Bye, Sparky.
Bye.
Natalie Rogers,
custom wreaths or um,
travel consultant.
Hi, it's Olivia.
Olivia.
I was just talking about you.
Are you back from Rome yet?
No, I am not back from Rome.
Uh, I guess you haven't
been following the news,
have you?
It's the big chill,
the new Ice Age.
What are you talking about?
I'm stranded here.
Oh no.
Yeah, looks like I won't be home
for Christmas, I'm so sorry.
It's okay, it's um
I'll miss you,
but don't worry about me,
lots of friends have offered to
spend their Christmases with me.
But are you okay?
Yeah, but I wanted to kinda keep
this as a surprise,
you know how I've been wanting
to open my restaurant for years.
Well, I finally convinced
Chef Grimaldi to come over
to Pine Valley
and be my partner.
I remember him
from when you took me to
Italy when I was little girl.
I always thought he looked
just like Santa Claus.
Oh, uh, so
my plan was to open
on Christmas Eve
with a big traditional
feast of Natale.
You know how it is
in small towns, nothing is
ever open on Christmas
and there's always
a few people with no
place to go.
No one should
be alone on Christmas.
Yeah, I feel terrible.
We already had a handful
of reservations I'm gonna
have to cancel, there's no
way Chef Grimaldi
can do it on his own.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, me too.
Well, I wanted to let you
know, Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas, Olivia.
Problems are just opportunities
in work clothes.
Hi, Mrs. Myers.
This is Natalie Rogers,
Olivia's cousin.
I have an idea.
What do you know about
this restaurant
she's planning on opening?
Come here.
Come on.
Alright.
Olivia always was an optimist.
Chef Rivaldi?
You stay here.
All dogs might go to
heaven but they should
probably stay out of
restaurant kitchens.
Stop right there, you
Ow!
No, don't, let me go!
Oh, that's so much better.
Are you hurt?
What?
No, no.
No.
II think it's fine.
Now get outta
my kitchen, presto.
Your kitchen, this is my cousin
Olivia's kitchen.
So Olivia has a cousin?
And the restaurant may
be hers, but the kitchen
always belongs to the chef.
You can't be Chef Grimaldi.
You're nothing like Santa Claus.
Oh, you're thinking of my uncle,
Zio Lorenzo Grimaldi.
Maybe I just look like my.
But he was too old to
come to America,
so I came instead.
Sorry, I'm his nephew
Stefano Grimaldi.
Ow.
Uh, sorry.
Uh, I don't know
the name of you.
I'm Natalie.
Rogers.
Olivia's cousin.
Oh, I should've known.
See Olivia told me her
cousin was
la bella signorina.
Oh, that's very nice of her.
Oh, and it's very true.
But what were you doing uh,
sneaking around my kitchen?
I wasn't sneaking.
Then that's not the word for it,
the sneaking and creeping.
No, I wasn't doing any of those
thing,
I was just looking for the chef.
Yoohoo!
Is anybody here?
Mrs. Myers.
Thanks for coming.
Have you met my
cousin's best friend?
- Hi.
- This is Mrs. Anna Myers.
Stefano!
Oh, I see you have.
And another one.
What third time's not a charm?
Stefano's quite charming enough.
And who is this?
Sparky.
I'm pet-sitting
for the holidays.
Well, it was nice
to see you, huh.
And to meet you, Sparky.
But I must go otherwise my
sauce, huh, it will burn
if I don't get back.
- Oh, I just need to talk to you.
- No!
A chef will never
let his food burn.
Not for anything.
Mamma mia.
Well, fine then.
I brought your cousin's spare
keys, I'm sure
she won't mind if you
stay in her house while
you're here in town.
Thank you.
I really wanna go through
with the grand opening
just as planned.
Well, there's a lot of
work to be done.
Every problem is an opportunity
in disguise.
If you insist.
Well, let's get you settled in
and I'll tell you
what I know of her plans.
Unless I was
interrupting something.
What?
No.
He's a very handsome man.
He's a very grumpy man.
He yelled at me in Italian.
And he doesn't even
look like Santa Claus.
What a cute store.
I know, lovely.
So nice.
You know, Olivia asked
me to cancel all
of the Christmas reservations
but if you're really serious
You bet I'm serious.
Olivia didn't wanna let
anyone down on Christmas
and neither do I.
Beebee, hello!
Hi, Mrs. Myers.
Beebee's one of my students.
This is my good friend's
cousin, Natalie.
How are you doing, Beebee?
Uh, not's so good.
I was hoping to get some temp
work in over vacation,
but it seems
like everyone in town has
already hired the holiday help.
Too bad.
I'll keep an ear around.
Thanks, Mrs. Myers.
It was nice to meet
you, Ms. Natalie.
Oh, there's
someone you should know,
Miles Croaker, he's out
town culture vulture.
Culture vulture?
You know, he oversees
all the town events,
concerts and reviews
everything from
the high school musical to
the local restaurants
for the paper.
Restaurant reviews, huh.
He's tough, but fair
and very well-respected.
He can make it work for
anyone in this town.
Phew.
Miles, dear,
what's the matter?
I haven't seen you this
distraught since the
fizzing fireworks fiasco of '09.
Oh, it's this Roman snow-blow.
Oh, the blizzard that hit Rome.
Yeah, my cousin's stuck
there for Christmas.
Oh, this storm's
has wreaked havoc on air
travel all over the world.
And in in Christmas.
Oh, our touring carolers
just heard that flights home
are canceled and
can't be rescheduled until
after the holiday.
It's terrible to be away
from home on Christmas.
Hmm, yes, I was
hoping they'd be able to
celebrate in the café,
it's closed on Christmas.
Are most places closed then?
Yes, all of them.
Our poor carolers aren't
just stranded without
their loved ones,
but must also eat microwave
turkey dinners.
Ew.
Mm-mm.
Can you please excuse me
I must call my travel agents
again and see if there's
anything they can do.
Those poor carolers.
I don't suppose
you can do anything
for their travel agent front?
I already tried
for my cousin Olivia,
everything's locked up.
It looks so beautiful.
You know Olivia,
she always has to set up
her decorations right after
Thanksgiving
that way Christmas can last as
long as possible.
You know she'd be here
if she could.
Yeah.
I know.
I just can't remember the
last time I celebrated
Christmas without her.
Oh, do you wanna stay
for dinner?
Of course.
I'm sure you can find something
in the freezer to cook.
Cook?
You did just wanna have a grand
restaurant opening, right?
Yeah, I just didn't think
I would be the one cooking.
I better take this.
Go ahead, make yourself at home.
Hey.
I know.
Lasagne.
Dishwasher, this is the oven?
I tried that one.
Okay.
Back to planning Pezzo Di Parma.
Who could that be?
- Stefano.
- Ciao, Natalie.
Uh, I made a sauce but uh,
now there is no one to eat it,
so I thought maybe
if you don't have any plans
for dinner,
you can have.
And some bone for the cagnolino.
Doggie bag for the doggie that's
very thoughtful, thank you.
Prego.
Oh, do you wanna come in
and join us for dinner?
There's gotta be plenty.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I was just making a lasa...
Oh no, the lasagne.
Oh.
Ooh, no!
Oh my gosh, I'm so sorry.
What are you
what is going on here?
I was just thawing the lasagne
and then I got uh,
distracted researching
for the grand opening
and I guess I just forgot.
Forgot?
Forgot.
Do you forget to breathe?
Does your heart forget to pump?
How can you be
cooking and forget?
I'm not much of a cook.
But I found so many
wonderful ideas, I didn't
realize how elaborate
the feast of Natale is.
There's a beautiful
celebration and everybody
comes together for a big
Christmas meal that lasts
for hours and hours with um,
antipasto, and salad,
and meats, and sweetbreads.
Mhmm.
And candied
nuts, and wine, music.
I thought we could
decorate the whole place
like a Tuscan villa but
with Christmas touches like a
Mm.
Looks like
Mmm.
Your mystery pasta worked
its magic again.
It's so
There's parsley and oregano.
What else?
It will be la specialità
Italia de casa
when we finally open
Pezzo Di Parma.
If we ever open.
Madame.
Of course, you're gonna open.
And just in time.
Just in time for Christmas.
What?
Yeah, like you
and Olivia planned.
No, it's impossible.
We have three days until
Christmas, we we-we
we have nothing prepared,
we have no staff,
no no decoration.
No food prepared,
it's impossible.
No, I have a lot of really good
ideas, if I
Stefano's right, Natalie.
It's a lovely idea,
but we don't have enough time
to get it done.
- It's okay.
- Maybe you're right.
Is it coriander?
Fennel?
Oh, come on,
you have to tell me.
If I tell you, it will not be
a mystery sauce anymore, right?
Mhmm.
But please.
Turmeric?
Paprika?
Na Natalie, the thing to
guess is the
a little bit in the cook.
Unlike your lasagne.
Capito.
Natalie, good morning.
Morning.
I fancy you're gonna need
our reservation book?
I better get started on those
cancellations.
Hmm.
Mr. Croaker, good morning!
Well, good morning.
I heard a rumor that your
cousin's restaurant might
be open for Christmas and
I thought I'd come
to see for myself.
I'm afraid that's just a rumor.
Oh, well, worth a try.
Oh, uh, sorry, my dear.
This is Ariella Cancio,
one of our touring carolers.
- Hello.
- Buongiorno.
Oh uh, I'm so sorry,
I forget my manners.
Um, I was just saying it
is sad this year,
so many of us have nowhere to go
but um,
meeting someone from the same
part of Italia
it's a little bit of home.
I'm afraid it is sad, but uh,
there's no way around it.
- Uh, sorry, we don't...
- Yes, there is.
Just a tiny change of plans.
Mr. Croaker, Ristorante Pezzo Di
Parma would be proud
to host you and all
of the carolers for a big
traditional feast of
Natale dinner on Christmas.
Oh, well, thank you.
Grazie mille.
- Ci vediamo.
Are you kidding?
Or do you wanna make the pasta?
Do you wanna make the pizza?
What are you gonna do, huh?
Pazza.
Pazzo.
Oh, but I can help.
Oh my God!
It's gonna be fine.
Woman make me crazy, eh.
Tried to tell you
it's impossible,
but you don't listen, huh.
Well?
Impossibile, impossibile.
There's always a way.
No, it will be a fiasco.
And that is...
It's the same word in English
and it will not be a fiasco,
there is always a way.
Sometime there is no...
There is no way.
Sometime there is a wall,
there's just a big wall
and no ladder, capisce?
Big wall or small,
the best way to get over it
is to start climbing.
Maybe you are crazy.
If we can pull this off
your mystery sauce alone
is worth a five-star review.
Reviews are important.
Many, many restaurant in
America they fail because
of it, I understand.
But I thought,
I thought I would have
more time to plan,
to make everything perfect.
It will be perfect.
And it will be a beautiful
feast of Natale for
a bunch of people that
have nowhere else to go.
I will get my recipes.
- Plan the menu.
- Great.
What should I do?
You?
You look for a rope.
Even if can get up that wall,
Natalie, we still need
a way down.
Okay, read me the list again.
Décor, so all this.
Food.
Oh, that's Stefano's department.
Believe me, you do not
want me doing the cooking.
Menus.
I can do those.
Beautiful handwritten
menus will be great, right?
Yeah.
Staffing.
Well, we aren't gonna have
a formal service for just five,
but we're definitely
gonna need some help now
even going family style.
Who do you think we can get
this close to Christmas?
Well, there's this guy
in my class.
Tyler.
But I don't know him that well.
Oh, then what makes you think...
Well, his cousin Melissa
told me that his folks
were going out of town, he was
supposed to join them
once school was out, but then
I heard from Joanna that
all the flights were canceled
due to the snowstorm in Italy.
And last year he was helping
stock shelves
at the hardware store, but then
I heard from Carol
that he didn't take the job this
year, 'cause he didn't
think he'd be around.
But you don't know him
very well?
Not really.
This Tyler, he's um pretty
cute, huh?
Yeah.
I mean I guess, I never
really paid attention
all that much.
Does he have curly brown hair?
Mhmm, I mean I...
I don't know him that well.
And warm puppy dog eyes?
Yeah.
How did you know that?
Um, because there's a cute boy
with curly brown hair
over there pretending
not to notice you
for the last 10 minutes.
Where?
What, no, no don't don't point.
Please tell me he didn't see me.
I think he sounds
like a great candidate.
Why don't you go offer
him the job?
I can't do that.
You should be the
one to do that.
As my assistant, I'm delegating
my task to you.
No, but I wouldn't even know
what to say.
You'll be fine, go on,
I'll help you.
- Please, no.
- I'll help you.
Tyler!
Hi, it's Beebee.
Jordan.
From school.
You know?
Oh, Beebee, hi, uh.
Yo, what's uh, what's up?
I'm so sorry, uh.
What's up?
Not much.
How are you?
I'm cool.
- What's that?
- No.
Just some reindeer went by,
you know, no big deal.
Reindeer, right.
Oh, I was wondering if you
wanted a job for the holidays?
You'd be working with me.
Not every second.
Just sometimes.
Only when we had to.
Uh, well, schp sch sure.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
- What's the - Cool.
What's the job?
What is it?
- Miming.
- Miming, uh,
I I I don't...
Serving food in a restaurant.
That yes, that I can do.
Yeah.
Good, 'cause there's also...
drumming.
Um.
Cooking!
Cooking, helping
cook in the kitchen.
I like to cook.
- Good.
- Yeah.
'Cause there also might be...
You know what,
here's my boss
Ms. Natalie right now.
Hey, Tyler.
Hi.
Beebee's told me a lot
about you even though
she doesn't know you very well.
Uh.
I think if you're
interested in the job,
you'd be a great fit.
It sounds great.
Great um, why don't you
head on over to
Pezzo Di Parma, I'll let
Stefano know
you're on your way.
Thanks, Ms. Natalie,
uh thank you.
Um, thanks Beebee.
I'll uh, I'll see you later.
Andiamo, Tyler.
Dry storage and cold storage,
prepping area.
Prepping area.
Hot line, cold line,
plating area.
- Capito?
- Yeah.
Love, life, and
cooking is all the same.
It's logical.
I'm looking at your face
and I see you don't understand.
Uh, no, no, I get
that cooking has to be
logical, but love?
Okay, I will use
myself as an example.
Tyler, I already know the woman
I will fall in love with.
How can you know that?
Logic.
I know it will be someone
who will help me raise
our children to speak Italian,
who wants to live where I live,
and love cooking
as much as I do.
So we can share our
second passion, pasta.
Okay, but what about you know,
attraction?
Ah, you want a bella
signorina, of course.
But not every bella
signorina is the right
bella signorina for you.
That why you need logic.
Wow, I haven't even
thought about what I want.
Hello?
Ah.
We're back.
We brought enough stuff
to deck the halls.
Oi.
Not to mention the dining room.
And even
you.
Hmm, that smells delicious.
And we are starving.
Good.
Then you must eat,
it's almost finished.
Is that the mystery sauce?
Ah.
Did you see what he put in it?
Oh, there was some...
There was some green stuff,
and some chopped stuff,
and uh, some other stuff.
Maybe if I eat out of the pan,
I'll get the mystery ingredient.
Nah!
Scusi.
Hmm.
Little bit sweet
and a little bit tangy
and just a tiny bit bitter,
but in a good way like
Si.
Ginger.
The mystery ingredient
is ginger, right?
Tell me I'm right.
Or maybe thyme.
If I told you
It wouldn't be a mystery.
What?
It doesn't have thyme,
but it needs it, right?
How could you give me advice on
the pompieri,
the firefighter, they must
put the boots on
when they are coming over, hmm?
Okay, okay.
I'm cooking-challenged.
But when I was a little girl,
Olivia used to make me
taste everything
that she went along.
Oh.
I actually have
a pretty good palate.
This is delicious.
It would be better
if I had Olio d'oliva descadoni.
It's an olive oil we make
in Parma next
to where I come from.
I looked for it everywhere,
I cannot find it.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Mamma mia.
Basta.
I still think the mystery
ingredient is ginger.
Turmeric!
I don't know much about
kitchens, but I know
that's not good.
And the plumbing is old here,
it needs an expert touch.
Oh God!
Oh God, oh.
Expert, huh?
Here let me.
It's probably just
one little pipe.
Tyler, Beebee,
go check the washroom.
Everything's gonna be fine.
It can't be all the plumbing.
Why not?
Um, because it's Christmas.
No water in the ladies room.
Or the men's.
We cannot open a restaurant
without running water.
Problems are just
opportunities in disguise.
No, basta.
The feast of Natale is off.
Any chance they'll finish
before Christmas?
Okay, thank you, yeah.
Yeah, Merry Christmas.
Come on, we got this.
This is just a chance to
show our awesomeness.
And we are pretty dang awesome.
Am I right?
Hello!
I brought that tree
skirt you wanted.
Do you know you still have
lasagne on the back stoop?
Uh, thank you.
I'm waiting until spring,
so I can give it
a proper burial.
You're the only person
I know that
uses a smoke alarm
instead of an egg timer.
Well, good thing
we have Chef Stefano.
Very good.
Actually I was wondering
if I could scrounge
an invitation to the festive
feast, if you have room.
Of course, you are more than
welcome to join us.
Thank you,
that pasta the other day,
it may mean that handsome
is as handsome does, but
that handsome des very
well in the kitchen.
So you finally noticed, huh?
Yeah, in the kitchen.
Mrs. Myers, you are terrible.
Besides, I think he's
interested in Ariella,
that caroler from Italy.
They seem to have
a lot in common.
Oh.
And once Olivia
comes back, I'm gonna go
back to the city.
That's 23 for dinner.
We invited the Serena Carolers
and Miles Croaker too,
of course.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
Yeah, one taste
of Stefano's mystery sauce
and he is sure to
give a rave review.
Miles Croaker has never
given any restaurant
a rave review.
Ever.
Oh.
The last restaurant
he banned, well...
What?
Closed within
a couple of months.
So what you're saying is
if we fail,
we risk totally destroying
Olivia's dream.
I'm afraid so.
Birds are out in full force.
Really glad you agreed we
need to have a Christmas tree.
Yeah, we have
Christmas tree in Italy,
too, you know?
I know.
I saw the Pinterest.
And this is it,
uh, this is our tree.
I don't know.
I do know.
The correct height, uh,
the correct amount around.
And the correct
amount of branches.
There's a correct
number of branches?
Yes.
Not so many,
there's not enough space for
decoration, but enough
space uh, to be like,
to be
Bushy.
Natalie, it's a tree not a bush.
Just doesn't feel right.
Feel?
What does feel have
to do with this?
It's all about logic like
life, uh cooking, like love.
Life is not about logic,
it's about
oh, what about this one?
Oh, why this one?
I don't know, my
instincts just tell me,
this is the right tree.
Yeah, I think your instinct uh,
mistaken.
My instincts are never wrong.
Huh?
Is that right?
Oh.
Oh, hmm.
Wait, did you
just say you think you can
rely on logic for love?
Of course.
What else?
Instincts.
Intuition.
That little voice inside
you that says you're at
the perfect place
at the perfect time.
And when that
has happened to you?
Well, it hasn't happened.
Not yet.
But it will.
What, it's not like logic's
really worked out
so well for you either.
It's it's really
hard to see under here.
Um, well, let me
get some lights, maybe
that'll help.
Um Tyler, Tyler!
Oh Tyler, are you okay?
Tyler, are you okay?
Tyler, are you hurt?
Are you all chopped up
like potato peelings?
Are you hurt?
Are you chopped up like
No, but I might be
deaf from here on out.
If you heard me
ask the question,
how can you be deaf?
What was that?
What was that
what was that ringing?
Nevermind the ringing,
what about the plumbing?
Huh, what?
What?
What drumming?
Plumbing, not drumming.
Oh, right.
Look, um, I'm sorry,
Beebee, I can't do this.
Tell Ms. Natalie I tried
but I guess they're gonna
have to cancel
the feast of Natale.
I'm sorry, alright?
Okay, hold on.
You can't give up.
Don't you see this is
a chance to prove
your awesomeness.
Awesomeness, I
I don't even know if I have
any awesomeness.
Well, here's your chance
to find out.
It's time to prove your
awesomeness, Tyler.
You can do this.
Okay.
Alright, you stand over there.
Okay!
Why?
Because if I do
find my awesomeness,
I wanna make sure it doesn't
get shredded in the
garbage disposal.
- No!
- Yes!
- No.
- Yes.
What if your intuition
never picks
a logical tree?
What if your logic never
picks a tree
that feels right?
What if intuition is broken?
What if your logic is just
stupid?
Have you thought about just
buying two trees?
Then you can both be right
and happy.
We do have room for it.
I wanna have all day,
so yes, thank you.
Okay, two trees it is.
Just call it when you
see the one you want.
- Okay, you too.
- Okay.
- Mine!
Natalie, hi, how are you?
Hey, Olivia, um
how's the Roman snow-blow?
Yeah, it's still blowing.
Oh.
Oh, what's wrong?
Did your plan for Christmas
with your friends fall through?
It uh, hasn't gone exactly
according to plan.
Um
I actually kind of have
a strange question for you.
Do you know where I could get
a bottle of Olio d'oliva
descadoni.
Well, that is a rare kind of
olive oil.
You are not gonna
try to cook, are you?
No.
Um, I just thought it
would make a nice gift for
um, for a friend.
Oh, you know,
'cause it's from Parma,
the same region as Chef
Grimaldi.
Oh, I had no idea.
Um, do you know where
I can find it in the State?
No, I do not know of any place
outside of Italy,
I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Well, that's okay.
Thanks anyway, Olivia.
Um, I have to go.
I miss you.
Merry Christmas.
I miss you, too.
Perfect.
Keys please.
Thanks.
Let's have a go,
moment of truth.
So much for my awesomeness.
No, Tyler, you've been great.
You really have.
I mean you know so much more
than you thought you did.
You think?
You've been great too, Beebee.
I never would've thought
about checking with the
city about the main line.
Thanks.
But
Yeah.
So I guess I'll
I'll see you back at
school in January.
Yeah.
January.
Bye.
Wait!
Did we remember to turn
the sink's off valve back on?
Yes, yes!
Alright, okay.
Alright, here we go.
- Yes!
Yes!
Oh, yes!
Just leave it there.
What is that?
I think that's
the sound of awesomeness.
Awesomeness?
Yes, oh yes!
- Is that good?
- It's very good.
Is there a plumber in the house?
Oh, Ms. Natalie, Tyler got
the water back on.
Yeah, and Beebee
helped, she was she was
Awes awesomeness.
Well, yeah.
Good, then we start
with the pasta.
Sure, yeah, I'm ready
to do anything.
No Tyler, you better go home
and shower
not work in the kitchen, huh?
Oh yeah, well, I guess yeah,
I'm sort of
Me too.
Yeah, you've done enough
for now.
Natalie will help
me with the pasta.
Me?
You do remember what
happened the last time
I tried to cook, right?
Don't worry,
Natalie, you're not cooking.
You're just making
the tortellinis.
I'll be the one cooking them.
Oh, okay, great.
In my country, Natalie,
the children do
this all the time.
I mean at least a child, si.
Si.
I mean yes.
Crack the egg into the flour.
Whoops, too hard.
- Uh, let me try - Si.
Si, si, si, si, si.
Another one.
Okay, let me try that again.
Bellissimo.
Perfecto.
Uh, now need to uh,
beat the egg up like you making
scrambled eggs,
but incorporating
the flour slowly.
Like this.
Oh, sure.
You never made scrambled eggs?
Yes, I have not.
How have you not
starved to death in that
city of yours?
Grabhub.
The pizza delivery boy.
Ai yai yai.
You know, if everybody stayed
home and cooked every night,
nobody would need to go
to a restaurant.
The egg is getting away.
Oh, ooh, hold on eggies,
get back here.
Back to your volcano.
Don't you wanna be part of
the best pasta
the world's ever known.
Good.
Well, now the pasta is mixed,
we need to knead it.
It's a very good workout,
my nonna,
my grandmother, she had
arms like a
like a Schwarzenegger.
Oh.
I'm not really sure
if that's a ringing
endorsement or not.
Ai, you have
to lean into it, uh.
Oh.
You need to feel it changing
under your hands.
Feel it changing?
I feel something.
Buongiorno, anyone here?
Here!
Uh yeah, we're over here.
Ariella.
Ciao bella.
The carolers and I just wanted
to drop off po di vino.
Not not for the feast of Natale
of course, but uh,
just an early grazie for
everything you are doing for us.
Prego.
Very thoughtful of you, grazie.
Yes, very, very thoughtful
of all of the carolers.
Please thank them for us.
And uh, what's all this?
Oh, you make pasta?
I used to make pasta with
mia nonna every Natale.
It uh, it was my favorite part.
But uh, I can help.
Oh, you cook?
Of course, I love to cook.
But you're our guest,
we couldn't possibly make you
work in the kitchen.
Make me, no, I want to.
We'd love your help.
Let me get you an apron.
Andiamo.
Okay.
Great.
Hmm.
They're waiting for us.
Okay, I'm ready.
Um, Chef Stefano.
How'd you come with your
logical list of
qualities you're looking
for in a woman?
Well, I thought about it
and she didn't make sense to me.
Why what's the matter?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
I just I guess I just
haven't done enough thinking.
Andiamo.
Baked brie with olive tabouli,
minestrone reteta,
ricotta and spinach tortellini,
braised beef in Merlot
wine sauce and something
called, "Panettone".
Sounds wonderful.
But I'm afraid Stefano's
multo-italiano menu
isn't gonna trigger any warm
American fuzzies.
I make these
really good cookie bars.
Well, it's a start.
I know, we can make
a big batch of cookies
and then take
the tray into the town
Christmas Cookie
Swap this afternoon.
Christmas Cookie Swap?
This afternoon?
Beebee, you just baked my day.
Ooh, but we're gonna have
to hurry
if we'll be ready on time.
Come on.
Just like shake some in.
Oh!
Okay.
All over.
Everywhere.
Oh, looks pretty great.
Perfect.
Good job.
Alright, to the fridge.
Now we just 30 minutes
while it sets.
You better set a timer,
can't rely on a smoke alarm
for this one.
So I ordered all the place cards
and the menu cards,
I know you wanted to write
them up by hand
but until Chef Stefano
finalizes the menu
Ms. Natalie.
It's like Olio d'oliva descadoni
is some kind of...
Ms. Natalie!
Culinary food myth,
like free-range foie gras
or guilt-free ice cream.
Ms. Natalie!
Oh, I'm sorry, what?
It's time.
Hurry, we're gonna
be late for the swap.
Okay, go, go, go!
Hats, coats, gloves, it's cold!
The secret to a clean
kitchen is simple,
don't cook ever.
Porca vacca!
What, what, oh sorry,
what happened?
What?
I can't see.
Holy cow!
That's what I said,
eh, not exactly,
but you get the idea.
What happened?
There's only one
thing I can think of that
can cause so much damage
to a kitchen
in so short of a time.
Rabid badgers?
Rabid badgers, Natalie!
Oh yeah.
Yeah, that make
that makes sense.
Well, look look at least
the smoke alarm isn't
going off yet.
This feast of Natale is not
gonna work.
Why do you say that?
Because we used
up our Christmas miracle
when Natalie didn't burn
the whole place down.
Okay, are we late,
did we make it on time?
Uh no, we made it.
Wooh.
There's free samples.
Don't say it.
That's because you're one
smart cookie.
Big beautiful bars, thank you.
Thank you.
Ooh, maybe we
should do two, alright?
Thank you.
Hmm, yummy.
They almost look like a little
reindeer poop or something.
- It it has to be.
- They're really good.
Yeah.
Gingerbread cookie.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas.
Beebee, did we forget
to turn the oven off
or something?
We never turned it on.
Oh, but maybe we
forgot to tidy up.
I didn't forget,
we really didn't have time.
Natalie, what is that?
What is this?
This cooking, huh?
Hmm?
I'm sorry,
I think we may have left
the kitchen a little not clean.
Not clean.
I come inside and I take
a look and I say
what'd I say... What I...
Oh, grande like grand,
a big a big mess.
Uh yeah, it's a big mess.
We have only one day left,
so much to do
and you run off for this.
Uh, why don't you take my half
and head back to the restaurant
and get started on the clean-up.
Hmm.
Explain to me.
Yeah, I'll help.
Oh, you don't have to do that,
it wasn't your mess.
No, no, I wanna help.
You do?
Yeah, Chef Stefano scares me
when he's like this.
I don't even know what these
cookies are?
Oh look, these are shortbreads
with a little um, icing drizzl,
and this little gingerbread man.
Little gingerbread man,
"Can't catch me,
I'm a gingerbread man."
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, Natalie.
This is an Italian feast
of Natale,
not the American
feast of cookie.
- Capito?
- Mhmm.
We will do panettone
made by my family recipe,
capisce?
- And the cookies.
- Mamma mia.
I read on Miles' reviews,
I think he would really like
Uh, Natalie.
Stefano.
Speak of the devil.
Hello.
- Ariella, ciao.
- Ciao, Stefano.
Mr. Croaker.
- Natalie, ciao.
- Hello.
Well, everybody is so excited
and looking forward
to your feast of Natale.
So are we.
We uh, we're just gonna
head back there and get
some things ready.
We want it all to
be just perfect.
That means you're coming to
the Christmas festival,
it's about to start.
Oh, no, no,
there is so much to do.
- Sorry, yeah.
- So much to do.
More than ever.
But it's our first
annual Christmas festival,
you must come.
We need everyone to
make it a success.
I organized it myself.
If you insist.
We'll be there with bells on.
- Like jingle bells.
- Oh.
Um, cool uh,
we'll just go get ready now.
- See you soon.
- Do that.
See you soon.
Alright, alright, this way.
Get on there.
Okay, you there.
Okay, ready.
Cheese.
- Yes!
- Congratulations!
Thank you.
Here.
Oh, you're here!
I have just the thing.
Right this way.
Oh uh, but first, picture.
Right, right, here we go!
Here we go, have to
keep the line moving.
Sit down, Sparky.
Sit down.
This one looks fun.
Oh yeah, sure.
Thanks.
Go first.
Sure, yeah.
Okay, wooh.
Aw.
No good, here let me try.
It's okay.
Do you feel okay?
Yeah.
How do I look like I'm feeling?
Well, I don't know,
but but nothing good.
So uh, have you seen
any good Kung fu movies lately?
Mm, nope.
Why?
Uh, just just curious.
What about baseball games?
In December?
Well, at least you know they
don't play baseball
in the winter.
Yeah, well,
that's all I know, so
Yeah, I forgot to
ask uh, about what you do
in the city?
What is your job?
Oh, I'm a Jacklyn of all trades.
I watch the dogs
and design custom prints,
do specialty gift-wrapping,
plan events and parties,
and about a hundred other
things.
Huh, why do you
do so many things?
Why don't you just do one thing?
I don't know,
I guess I just never found
the right thing and so
I kept trying new things.
Hmm, when I was 3 years old
my Zio Lorenzo,
he put a knife in my hand
and I knew I would be a chef.
That is all I ever wanna be.
Your Zio Lorenzo
gave a butcher's knife to
a 3-year-old?
No.
Maybe I exaggerate
a little bit, huh?
Well, maybe
you're exaggerating now.
Maybe you're afraid, huh?
I'm not scared of anything.
Except perhaps the cold, yes?
It's not that bad.
No, you're cold.
What's that?
What's what?
The piece of paper
you keep checking.
What, what piece of paper?
The one in your pocket.
Um
Catch!
No!
Beebee, Beebee, no, no, no, no.
Don't, don't.
Oh, what is it,
a letter to Santa?
Don't just don't just don't
just don't just
can can you give it back
to me please, Beebee?
What is this?
"My smile, awesomeness,
likes baseball."
What is this, like a list
of things I'm supposed to be
or something?
No, it's...
I'm not hardly
any of these things.
Beebee, it's not
like that, it's just...
I was just trying to be logical,
that's all.
You're a jerk.
Beebee.
Beebee, what's the matter?
What happened?
Are you okay?
It's Tyler, he's being
really logical.
I can't
Okay, let's go have some cocoa,
you can tell me about it.
Grazie.
Why don't you
start at the beginning?
We were at the Santa
sling booth and I was
I was trying to figure out
how Tyler felt about me.
He started asking all
these stupid questions
about Kung fu, baseball,
checking
his stupid list.
He said he was just trying
to be logical.
But then he can't possibly
like me,
I don't like any of the things
on the stupid list,
especially
not the nice smile part.
Oh.
Beebee, hey.
Your smile is lovely
just how it is, I promise.
What could give Tyler such
a silly idea like this?
"Speaks Italian,
lives at the same place,
loves to cook."
You okay?
Yeah.
Of course, um,
what happened next?
Well, I decided my intuition
was telling me
Tyler is a jerk and I left.
But maybe you should
just sleep on it, yeah?
Give your intuition some
time to think it over.
Yeah, I think I'll do that.
Christmas is exhausting.
Everything okay?
You know, I think I'm just gonna
go back to the restaurant.
But the festival is important.
Si.
And Natalie is here, too.
But we were thinking uh,
we're gonna go back,
it's there's so much to do.
Oh no, you don't have to go,
too.
You can stay,
I'm sure you want to.
What, and let
you do all the work?
No.
What if you try to cook
and burn the entire place
down to the ground?
It is time to sing.
You must come,
you need to with me.
Ooh, Sparky.
Sorry.
Sorry, Sparky.
Grazie.
Natalie!
Where are you going?
Home.
The festival just started,
uh, you don't like it.
Look, can I ask you something?
Yes.
Can we just keep
things strictly business
between the two of us?
Strictly business?
I know something is
wrong, I can tell.
And it is a word for it uh,
a word that is not a word.
Uh, you are eh.
A fork?
Hangry.
You need to eat and Sparky, too.
Let's go to Pezzo Di Parma,
I will cook
for the both of you, let's go.
Listen, I said I just wanna keep
things strictly business.
What how?
How strictly business?
Business is food,
food is business for me.
How is it not strictly business?
The thing is I don't know
if we're really
ready to be a business.
I mean I don't know
if we're really ready to do
a big feast of Natale,
not for this many people
and not for Miles who's never
given a rave restaurant
review in his entire life.
He hasn't, not ever?
No.
And I read all of them
and worse,
every place he pens,
it shuts down.
Natalie, I put
every bit of money
I have in Pezzo Di Parma.
I didn't know that.
And if we close, Natalie,
it's worse uh,
I cannot stay in America,
I have to go back to Italy.
See, we uh
we can't do this to you.
Or to cousin Olivia,
we can't ruin your dreams
before they've even begun.
Now you think my food is not
good enough, huh?
That's not what I'm saying,
I just we don't have
the time or the people
And this is why you don't
want to come to eat now?
It's not about that,
I just don't
- Natalie.
- What?
If my food is
not good enough for you,
certo is not good
enough for anybody.
Anybody.
The feast of Natale,
Natalie, is off.
Fine.
Fine!
- It's off!
- Okay.
God, stupid Stefano.
Come on, Sparky.
Come.
Panettone, panettone.
I'll make panettone,
it'll make me feel better.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, come on.
This way, this way.
Ooh, Natalie.
What are you doing here?
Uh, Mr. Croaker,
there is something I need
to tell you and um,
I thought I should probably
say it in person.
I'm very sorry.
And please don't hold this
against my cousin Olivia
or Stefano, but
Um
Uh, what's wrong?
Has something happened?
Stefano, you didn't have
to come,
I can take care of this myself.
This is not only
your cousin Olivia restaurant,
it it's also mine.
Has someone had bad news?
Oh, oh no, nothing
like that, they're just
missing their friends
and family because
it's Christmas.
I thought singing might
cheer them up,
but uh, it's made things worse.
Cassie has never spent
a Christmas away from her
children before.
Oh, and this was supposed
to be Charlie's first Christmas
with his new fiancé.
Oh no, that's so sad.
There'll be other Christmases,
but right now
it's hard for them all
to be far away from home.
But everyone is looking forward
to your Christmas meal tomorrow.
Now what is it you wanted
to tell me?
Could you excuse
us just one minute?
I feel terrible.
Yeah, me too.
I wanted to do everything
my own way,
just the right review,
but now look at this.
I wanted to show
Olivia how much her help
and support meant to me
and I guess I thought
I could only do that
if everything was perfect.
I think I kind of lost seeing
that's it's Christmas.
Yeah, yeah, it's Christmas.
And the kitchen.
Yes, in there, too.
What if we just
go through with it?
What if we don't worry
about if it's perfect or
what the review says, what
if we just do it to feed
a bunch of sad people that
have nowhere else
to go on Christmas?
Yes, yes.
Let's do it for the people.
And we need to be happy,
it's Christmas.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Let's do it.
Natalie, Stefano, uh
you had something to tell us?
Yeah, just that the feast of
Natale is at 1:00
and to bring your appetites.
It's gonna be awesomeness.
Hello, Natalie Rogers,
travel consult
oh um, events planning,
um actually Jacklyn
of all trades,
just uh tell
me which one you want.
The Olio d'oliva descadoni?
Yeah.
I've been looking
for it everywhere.
Back-ordered?
Until when?
July.
Oh um, oh.
Okay, thanks anyways.
You wanna tell me
what's got you so despondent
over this olive oil?
Olivia!
- Hi.
Oh, but how?
Oh, they finally
dug Rome out from under
that avalanche, I got the
first flight I could.
Why are you here?
I thought you were spending
Christmas with your friends
in the city.
I was, but I don't know I know
how hard you worked and how much
this means to you,
so I just...
Oh, it's so beautiful.
Thank you.
But why?
It's a long, long story.
Oh.
Is it now?
Well, that's good,
'cause I am a long,
long listener.
Well, even after...
22 phone calls,
and a dozen international
emails,
and millions of hours scouring
the internet,
I still couldn't find the Olio
d'oliva descadoni,
so Stefano could have his
perfect Christmas.
Do you like Stefano?
No!
I mean I like him.
I don't like-like him.
He's kinda grumpy sometimes.
Oh.
So you don't like him?
Even if I did,
I have to go back to the city.
I have a life there and
I don't know,
I can't stay here.
You're jumping again.
I'm what?
You do this thing
where you leap from job to job,
city to city.
What are you afraid of?
I'm not scared of anything.
Falling in love can be scary.
Well, it's been a long flight
and an even longer day
and I think tomorrow
is gonna be really,
really exciting.
Let's go home.
Oh, I'm so glad
you could make it home in
time for Christmas.
Me too.
Oh, um and if you
see any lasagne in the yard,
could you just ignore it?
You did try to
cook again, didn't you?
Uh, yeah.
It's good that
you reach for the stars.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Sorry.
Natalie.
I'm sorry.
Your terribleness in
the kitchen is contagious.
Uh, you'll be
glad I said something.
Merry Christmas.
Thank you.
Oh, you should open that now.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
Oh.
You didn't have to do that.
Come on, bella signorina first.
If you insist.
Is this the recipe
for the mystery sauce?
You're actually giving
away the mystery?
Yeah, and this way you don't lie
awake at night wondering.
Rosemary.
Of course.
How did I not guess that?
Maybe when you go
back to your city, you can
find someone somehow
who can cook it for you.
Not just a pizza
delivery boy, huh?
Capito?
Okay.
Your turn.
Olio d'oliva descadoni.
Natalie.
Grazie.
What's it smell like?
Like home.
I'm sorry you couldn't
be home for Christmas.
I know, this is my home now.
I still think you could use
a pinch of thyme.
Where are the little elves?
- Tyler was here - Be here.
He told me that he needed to add
something outside, I don't know.
Okay.
Merry Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
Are you guys
ready to get to work?
- Mhmm, mhmm, yeah.
- Sure, totally ready.
Great.
Places, everybody.
Turns out that he likes braces.
Gonna give you
a little bit more that,
a little bit more, mix it in.
They're almost here!
Merry Christmas!
Ciao, Natalie.
Buon Natale!
Welcome to
Ristorante Pezzo Di Parma.
Yep, one more.
I can take that, no problem.
- Merry Christmas.
- Thank you, merry Christmas.
Uh, find a seat.
They should be labeled.
Go.
Alright, fair, fair.
Yes, I just got my haircut.
Emma, I like your uh,
- Uh - My necklace.
Necklace, yeah, oh it's bella.
Oh, thank you,
thank you very much.
Um, they're um, not real.
They look real?
Yeah.
Ooh, formaggio.
Ooh, that looks good.
I know I'm so hungry,
I'm very
They're almost
done with the antipasto,
how's the soup coming along?
It's just about.
Okay, yep, mhmm.
Not yet, not yet.
Oh we can we
It's just about.
Okay, go.
That was suspenseful.
This is for you.
You need to keep
up your strength.
Cocoa with whipped cream
and nutmeg.
How'd you know
my favorite cocoa?
Hey, I know.
I asked cugina Olivia.
Even with everything else
you had to do?
- Thank you.
- Prego.
Mmm.
Scusi.
- What's so funny?
- Niente, niente.
Do I have food in my teeth?
Uh, not your teeth, no.
Alright.
Can you get me
a napkin or something?
Si, si.
Now didn't I remember that
there was a polar bear
- in your driveway one time?
- Not anymore, not anymore,
I since I've moved here
Oh, thank you.
We saw one last night, we did.
Please try the pasta.
We it's a family recipe.
- I hope you like it.
- Mangiamo.
Does he like it?
Huh.
Hmm.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have been reviewing
restaurants for over 20 years.
It has been my privilege
to dine in some of the finest
establishments in this country.
And in that time I have
never, not once,
tasted a perfect dish.
Until now.
Bravo to the chef.
Take your bow.
Oh, come on, Chef.
Take your bows.
Thank you, thank you very much.
Hope you enjoyed.
- Thank you.
- Grazie.
Natalie, may I speak
with you a moment?
Yeah, of course.
Uh, alone.
Sure.
Um, over here.
Everything okay with the meal?
Can I get you anything else?
Oh, it's the most
wonderful feast of Natale
I've ever had.
Not about that I want
to ask you.
It is uh,
you do not actually work
for Pezzo Di Parma,
this is correct?
That's right.
I have my own business.
Or businesses really,
in the city.
Good.
I am hoping that Stefano
will offer me a job
once you return to the city.
But you're singing.
I like Stefano.
Oh.
I see.
You are friends with Stefano?
Do you think that maybe
he likes me?
I don't know.
Um, I
I think you're perfect for him.
Beautiful.
Exquisite.
Stefano.
Ah, it'll be ready in a minute.
Great, um, maybe you can give
Ariella a minute
to talk to you.
And you might wanna look at this
in case you forgot.
Grazie.
Ciao.
We need to change it.
Thyme.
Really?
You took my advice?
Only because uh, it was right.
Natalie.
Why so sad on Christmas?
I'm not sad.
I'm happy for you and Ariella.
Me and Ariella?
Of course.
She likes you,
you have to know that.
Yes.
And I told her I was
happy to give her a job.
Not all my heart.
But she fits right in with your
philosophy of logic, and love,
life, and cooking.
She fits your list to a tee.
Natalie, my philosophy
has changed.
To what?
Panettone!
The panettone!
What happened?
Panettone, I burned
the panettone.
But a chef never lets
his food burn.
Not for anything.
I forgot.
How could you forget?
What are we gonna do
about dessert?
They're almost finished
with the main course.
We know.
The cookies.
Aha.
Try the red ones.
Alright.
There is a family
tradition that we have
where you go around
the dinner table
and say what the best part of
this Christmas is.
I guess I'll go first.
Um, for me the best
part of this Christmas
is being able to get home
in time
to share it with all of you.
And my cousin Natalie,
and my friend Stefano,
who made all of this possible.
The best part of this Christmas
has been sharing
this meal with all of you all
and my elastic waistband
which made all of it possible.
Cheers.
Oh, um my favorite part
of this Christmas
is um, well,
I've always kind of been
jumping around from job to job,
waiting for
something to tell me that
I finally have found
the perfect thing.
And nothing ever
felt quite right.
But this year, this Christmas
um, I finally found a place that
feels like home.
And someone
I'd really like to
share it with.
Stefano.
My favorite part
of this Christmas,
uh well
You, Natalie.
It is this.
Why are we all watching?
Oh my gosh!